[
  {
    "question": "In Switzerland, what animal delivers Easter eggs to kids?",
    "options": ["The sheep", "The cuckoo", "The goat", "The bear"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "In what country did the tradition of the Easter Bunny originate?",
    "options": ["Germany", "The United States", "Belgium", "Italy"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Easter Island is part of which country?",
    "options": ["Chile", "Colombia", "Peru", "Argentina"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "When were Cadbury Creme Eggs introduced?",
    "options": ["1956", "1978", "1941", "1963"],
    "correct": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "The Sunday before Easter is called what?",
    "options": ["Pre-Easter", "Good Sunday", "Palm Sunday", "Easter Sunday"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "From what is the filling in Cadbury Creme Eggs made?",
    "options": ["Cream cheese", "Fondant", "Melted chocolate", "Custard"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What egg-shaped candy was illegal in the United States?",
    "options": ["Cadbury Creme Eggs", "Kinder Surprise", "M&M Eggs", "Lindt Chocolate Eggs"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "What flower is most commonly associated with Easter?",
    "options": ["Lily", "Baby's-breath", "Tulip", "Daffodil"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which country is credited with starting the tradition of the Easter egg hunt?",
    "options": ["United Kingdom", "Germany", "United States", "Australia"],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "n which country is it traditional to have a large Easter Sunday feast, with lamb as the centerpiece?",
    "options": ["Turkey", "Italy", "Spain", "Greece"],
    "correct": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which animal is often featured in Easter-themed decorations and represents springtime?",
    "options": ["Duck", "Fox", "Deer", "Rabbit"],
    "correct": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "In the United States, which holiday immediately follows Easter Sunday?",
    "options": ["Labor Day", "Mother’s Day", "April Fool's Day", "Earth Day"],
    "correct": 4
  },
  {
    "question": "Which popular springtime treat is made by marshmallows shaped like chicks and bunnies?",
    "options": ["Cadbury Creme Eggs", "Jelly Beans", "Peeps", "Tootsie Rolls"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the term for the week leading up to Easter Sunday?",
    "options": ["Holy Week", "Spring Week", "Lenten Week", "Resurrection Week"],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "Which color is traditionally associated with Easter?",
    "options": ["Blue", "Pink", "Yellow", "Purple"],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "Which famous artist created a series of Easter-themed paintings of eggs?",
    "options": ["Vincent van Gogh", "Claude Monet", "Salvador Dalí", "Pablo Picasso"],
    "correct": 2
  },{
    "question": "Which U.S. state is home to the largest Easter egg hunt in the world?",
    "options": ["Florida", "Texas", "Tennessee", "Georgia"],
    "correct": 3
  }
]
